Overland Park, KS 66204 | 954-465-9162 | gregstead@gmail.com | github.com/gregstead | linkedin.com/in/gregstead/

Summary

Full stack web developer trained in legacy technologies and the modern MERN stack. Professional strengths include creative problem-solving, written and verbal communication, and versatility. Disciplined and detail-oriented mindset from 10+ year career as a classical musician.

Technical Proficiencies

JavaScript, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Handlebars, AJAX, React.js, Node, Express, MySQL, MongoDb, Python, Git, Heroku, Responsive Design

Projects

Employee Tracker

Video Demonstration: https://drive.google.com/file/d/13UkrkMyw6L76u-xx7RKj9JRczUeB1LFZ/view GitHub Repository: https://github.com/gregstead/12 employee tracker

- Command line interface for an employee database. Built with Node.js and MySQL.

Leave a Note

Deployed Project: https://project-leave-a-note.herokuapp.com/
GitHub Repository: https://github.com/BenjDG/Leave_A_Note

- Group message board. Built with Node.js, Express.js, Sequelize, MySQL, Handlebars.js. Automated testing and deployment with Semistandard.js, Passport.js, Heroku, Git/GitHub.

DiscomfortZone

Deployed Project: https://gregstead.github.io/discomfort_zone/
GitHub Repository: https://github.com/gregstead/discomfort_zone/

- WebApp that takes user input and provides suggestions for bars and restaurants. Built using JavaScript, HTML, Google Materialize CSS Framework, the TravelTime Time-Map API, and the TomTom Search API

Recent Work Experience

Amusement Connect Kansas City, Missouri

Arcade Technical Support Representative 02/2020–present

- Improved the training and workflow for future employees by documenting workflows and writing training manuals. Recognized by management for high performance with promotions.

Donnelly College Kansas City, Kansas Adjunct professor 08/2019–12/2019

- Guided students to a greater appreciation of music by introducing them to fundamental musical analysis techniques and presenting recordings in lectures, emphasizing cultural and historical contexts.

The Friends of Chamber Music, Kansas City Box Office and Concert Production Manager

Kansas City, Missouri 01/2017–05/2019

- Reporting directly to the founder, artistic director and CEO, was responsible for all concert production and venue readiness, planned and executed a ~\$500k budget. In addition, assisted in artistic planning, edited marketing copy, and project managed the annual program book.

Education

Full-Stack Flex Coding Boot Camp Certificate 03/2021 (expected)

University of Kansas Lifelong & Professional Education; Overland Park, Kansas

Master of Music 05/2014

Lynn University; Boca Raton, Florida

Bachelor of Arts in Music, *cum laude* 05/2011

Florida State University; Tallahassee, Florida